There are errors and bugs in this version that we are trying to fix as soon as possible.
These errors include:
*At first, make sure that you must log in at every stage of the game, and use a new username and password. Otherwise, there will be a problem in the operation of the program!
* Timers have a problem! (You will encounter it yourself)
* After exiting the game and re-entering another game, the content of the file that saved the users' points will be deleted (the information of the previous game will be deleted!) So before starting a new game, go to the profile section and the points earned in the previous game see that.

در این نسخه خطاها و باگ هایی وجود دارد که ما در تلاشیم  تا آنهارا هرچه زودتر رفع کنیم
این خطاها عبارتند از:
*در ابتدا مطمئن شوید که حتما در هر مرحله از بازی که نیاز است لاگین کنید، حتما از نام کاربری و پسورد جدید استفاده کنید . در غیر این صورت در کارکرد برنامه خلل ایجاد میشود!
*تایمر ها مشکل دارند! (خودتان با آن مواجه خواهید شد)
*پس از خروج از بازی و ورود مجدد به بازی دیگری، محتوای فایلی که امتیاز کاربران را ذخیره کرده است پاک میشود (اطلاعات بازی قبل پاک میشود!) پس پیش از شروع بازی جدید به بخش پروفایل رفته و امتیاز های کسب شده در بازی قبل را مشاهده کنید